we talk about this like we're going to
win but we just was in time if I could
just get inside of your
mind if you would just let me in I know
that life has a
way of turning things upside down I've
seen you lost and I've seen you found
[Music]
today I locked myself
inside I just had to get away from it
all it's not that I wanted to
hide I just don't want you to see me
fall life has in love ups and
downs and we don't need to be like that
you know what love way s you're
[Music]
back so time my
love in a tight time
mind time my love in a
tight
night cuz you never
know when you're going to need it most
and you'll never
F just another
go you light of the past you light of
the past you light of the past with your
love you light of the past you light of
the past with your love
[Music]